<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Conrad&#39;s Website</title>
    <link>http://conrads.website/posts/index.xml</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Conrad&#39;s Website</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 30 May 2018 23:04:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://conrads.website/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>In Stone</title>
      <link>http://conrads.website/posts/stone/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 May 2018 23:04:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://conrads.website/posts/stone/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I always find myself here. Laying in bed, waiting for the day to roll over as I do. Twisting and turning, I can never find the right position to begin falling asleep. Though my eyes can barely lift their lids, my head isn&amp;rsquo;t ready to call it quits - for today that is.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I always find myself here. Fingers on keys, eyes on the screen, though it keeps burning. I write my stream of thoughts into ones and zeros, kept understandable by the unicode standard (at least a little).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I always find myself here. At the junction of passing thoughts. One to describe reality as the motion and interactions of energy, nothing more. And another, that has already passed me by. I guess it&amp;rsquo;s only nothingness now.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I always find myself here. Wanting to be one person: cohesive, homogeneous, singular and unchanging. Wanting to be capable of finishing my plans, wanting to know who I am. Occasionally I stumble upon my old skin, where I used to live. Sometimes it still fits, though I always tear it. I can&amp;rsquo;t go back to the old me. Last week was a lifetime ago, tomorrow is in a couple of minutes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I always find myself here. Trying to write my words into stone, so that I can reflect and grow. My words are carved slow, as does rebuilding my hope. Hope - just as my words, exists only as wind.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Until I capture it in stone.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What to Expect Here</title>
      <link>http://conrads.website/posts/expectations/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://conrads.website/posts/expectations/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In all honesty, few processes of my head are consistent. That being said&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I do write poetry more often than other things, so expect more of that.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;By having a blog readily available, I might actually contribute&amp;hellip;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;There&amp;rsquo;s a lot of Computer Science topics that I want to share.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you&amp;rsquo;ve read my About page then you know that I don&amp;rsquo;t like reinventing wheels. But did you know that I&amp;rsquo;m also on Medium? ;)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Again, consistency is not a Conrad thing unless I document &lt;em&gt;everything&lt;/em&gt; about what I was thinking at the time. So I&amp;rsquo;ll probably be posting personal projects here too in case I ever want to go back to something.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>