<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Conrad&#39;s Website</title>
    <link>http://conrads.website/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Conrad&#39;s Website</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 01 Aug 2018 16:17:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://conrads.website/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Mathematical Seashells</title>
      <link>http://conrads.website/posts/seashells/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Aug 2018 16:17:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://conrads.website/posts/seashells/</guid>
      <description>In Seashells: The Plainness and Beauty of their Mathematical Description, Jorge Picado describes the mathematics necessary to simulate the shape of a multitude of different seashells. In this post, I wanted to share some renders I created while implementing Picado&amp;rsquo;s math into SciView and how the fourteen parameters function.
Defining the Spiral The parameters D, A, alpha and beta allow us to construct any variety of spiral we want.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>In Stone</title>
      <link>http://conrads.website/posts/stone/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 May 2018 23:04:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://conrads.website/posts/stone/</guid>
      <description>I always find myself here. Laying in bed, waiting for the day to roll over as I do. Twisting and turning, I can never find the right position to begin falling asleep. Though my eyes can barely lift their lids, my head isn&amp;rsquo;t ready to call it quits - for today that is.
I always find myself here. Fingers on keys, eyes on the screen, though it keeps burning. I write my stream of thoughts into ones and zeros, kept understandable by the unicode standard (at least a little).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What to Expect Here</title>
      <link>http://conrads.website/posts/expectations/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://conrads.website/posts/expectations/</guid>
      <description>In all honesty, few processes of my head are consistent. That being said&amp;hellip;
 I do write poetry more often than other things, so expect more of that.
 By having a blog readily available, I might actually contribute&amp;hellip;
 There&amp;rsquo;s a lot of Computer Science topics that I want to share.
  If you&amp;rsquo;ve read my About page then you know that I don&amp;rsquo;t like reinventing wheels. But did you know that I&amp;rsquo;m also on Medium?</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>